One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
A Woman's Honor
شرف المرأة
We managed to make it to the sea.
نجحنا في الوصول إلى البحر
Yeah.
أجل
Now to just get to back to the Sunny.
كل ما تبقى هو بلوغ السفينة فحسب
Juice River Sweet City
نهر العصير مدينة الحلوى
It's so sweet, I'm really happy!
حلوة للغاية، إنني سعيد
What? I don't like it. It's sticky all over...
لا تعجبني، فلزوجتها تغطي المكان
See? The helm is slippery...
أترى؟ إنّ الدفة زلِقة
Watch out! Move out of my way, fish-san !
احذري، ابتعدي عن طريقي أيتها الأسماك-سان
Brook! Isn't that a mermaid?!
بروك، أليست تلك حورية؟
What?! A mermaid-san ?!
ماذا؟ حورية-سان؟
Oh, it's a merman!
إنّه ذكر
Oh...
هكذا إذًا
What is he doing? Fishing, maybe?
ما الذي يفعله؟ ربما يصطاد؟
I don't care anymore...
لا يهمني أمره
Southwestern Coast The Seducing Woods
الساحل الجنوبي الغربي غابة الإغواء
As long as Big Mom is on a ravenous rampage, all we can do is run!
طالما بيغ مام مهتاجة من نوبة الجوع، فما بيدنا حيلة سوى الهرب
"Ravenous rampage"? What's that?
نوبة جوع؟ ماذا يعني ذلك؟
She's having a tantrum!
إنّها نوبة غضب
Until she can eat what she craves...
...حتّى تتناول ما تشتهيه
she'll keep rampaging without discretion!
فسوف تواصل الهيجان دون اكتراث
Wedding...
...كعكة
cake!
الزفاف
She's almost unconscious...
إنّها شبه فاقدة للوعي
What she craves this time seems to be a wedding cake!
ويبدو أنّ ما تشتهيه هذه المرة هي كعكة الزفاف
Maybe because she didn't get to eat the cake at the wedding!
ربما سبب نوبتها هو عدم تمكنها من تناول الكعكة أثناء الزفاف
Luffy! You shouldn't have ruined the cake!
لوفي، لم يكن يجب عليك إفساد الكعكة
But the plan succeeded!
ولكن الخطة نجحت
And I've never gotten to eat such a delicious cake before!
كما أنّه من النادر تناول كعكة لذيذة كتلك
Were you eating during the mission?!
أكنت تأكل أثناء المهمة؟
I ate it too! It was delicious!
أنا أيضًا تناولت منها، كانت لذيذة جدًّا
Anyway, hurry up! I'm sure we're close to the Sunny !
أسرعوا على أيّ حال، لا بدّ أنّ السفينة ليست ببعيدة
It's really hard to tell if we're going straight through these woods!
لكن يصعب علينا معرفة الاتجاه الصحيح داخل هذه الغابة
Is this really the right way?!
أمتأكدون أنّ هذا الطريق الصحيح؟
Oh! Look!
انظروا
That river looks familiar!
يبدو ذلك النهر مألوفًا
The Sunny must be right across the river!
لا بدّ أنّ السفينة على الجانب الآخر من النهر
Wait a minute!
انتظروا قليلًا
If I'm remembering right, that bridge was broken before!
لقد انهار ذلك الجسر حسبما أذكر
You're right...
معكِ حق
If these woods are our enemy, we can't trust anything!
ينبغي ألّا نثق بما حولنا طالما الغابة عدوتنا
They're trying to fool us...
إنّهم يحاولون خداعنا
so I'm sure they're shifting the landscape to confuse us...
لا بدّ أنّهم غيروا تضاريس الغابة لتشتيتنا
In other words,
بعبارةٍ أخرى، هذا المكان ليس بالمكان الذي نخاله
Lola's vivre card won't help us anymore...
إنّ الفيفر كارد الخاصة بلولا لم تعد مفيدة
Yeah, since Mama herself is right behind us!
هذا لأنّ ماما تطاردنا بنفسها
That gives you all the more reason to keep feeding him, Nami.
لذا عليكِ مواصلة إطعامه يا نامي
Yeah... Zeus!
أجل، زيوس
It's delicious! So delicious!
لذيذة، لذيذة
If we let Zeus go back to Mama, there's no way we'll be able to escape.
إن عاد زيوس إلى ماما، فلن تكون لدينا أدنى فرصة للهروب منها
Come back, Zeus!
عُد يا زيوس
If we're too slow, she'll catch up!
إن سرنا بهذه الوتيرة البطيئة، فستمسك بنا
Oh, no! I'm gonna get scolded!
سيئ، سأتعرض للتوبيخ
Hey!
أنت
Prometheus!
بروميثيوس
Why are you disobeying Mama's orders, Zeus?!
لِمَ تعصي أوامر ماما يا زيوس؟
Zeus! Look at me!
زيوس، انظر إلي
I've got an exquisite Weather Egg filled with juicy thunderclouds!
إنّها بيضة الطقس الفاخرة والمليئة بالسحب الرعدية العصيرية
Wow! That looks great!
تبدو شهية
Whoa, wait, Zeus!
مهلًا يا زيوس
Hey, sun!
يا شمس
How dare you...
...كيف تجرؤ
burn up the tree guy!
على حرق الشجرة؟
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Hawk Gatling!
رشاش الصقر
That's our Luffy!
كما هو متوقع من لوفي
What the...?!
ماذا؟
Don't think...
...إيّاك أن تظن
that you can beat me with just that!
أنّك ستهزمني بسهولة
Oh! Ow, ow, ow!
حار، حار، حار
If armament haki doesn't work, he'll be harder to deal with than a logia!
إن لم يؤثر به هاكي التسلح فهو أصعب من متناولي فاكهة اللوغيا
I'm gonna burn you all to death!
سأحرقكم حتّى الموت
Ow, ow! It's hot! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
حار، حار، حار، حار
Come back, Zeus!
عُد يا زيوس
I will! I will, but...
...سأعود، سأعود، ولكن
I wanna eat just one more juicy thundercloud!
أود تناول قطعة أخيرة من السحابة الرعدية الشهية
You...
...أيها
Jinbe!
جينبي
Cross the bridge now, everyone!
اعبروا الجسر حالًا يا رفاق
Okay!
حسنًا
Spear Wave!
موجة الرمح
Rain Shower!
وابل القرش
Did it work?!
هل نجح؟
Of course!
بالطبع
He's just a mass of compressed fire,
إنّه كتلة عادية مكوّنة من النيران
which makes him nothing but a big, talking flame.
يمكنك اعتباره مجرد شعلة ثرثارة
You bastard...
عليك اللعنة
Are they...?!
...هؤلاء
Mobile
موبايل
Kato
كاتو
Get ready, Straw Hat crew!
جهزوا أنفسكم يا طاقم قبعة القش
Compo
كومبو
The Seducing Woods will be...
...فهذه الغابة ستكون
Laurin
لورين
...where you die!
مقبرتكم
Tablet
تابلت
High-Fat Drop dead!
اهلكوا
What?! I can't believe they caught up to us!
مُحال، كيف سبقونا؟
The homies must've shifted the landscape!
لا بدّ أنّ الهوميز غيروا تضاريس الغابة
They're closing in from both sides...
حوصرنا من الجانبين
Then we only have one option...
إذًا ليس بجعبتنا سوى خيار واحد
Yeah, let's kick their asses!
أجل، لنُبرحهم ضربًا
Your name's Pedro, right? I saw you five years ago, too...
أنت بيدرو، صحيح؟ لقد رأيتك قبل خمس سنوات
You silly rabbit!
أيتها الأرنبة المزعجة
Garchu!
غارتشو
Stop!
توقفي
Yes!
مرحى
Brother Tablet!
أخي تابلت
You'd better pay attention!
يجدر بك الانتباه
Diable Jambe!
ساق الشيطان
Flambage Shot!
الركلة الملتهبة
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Eagle Bazooka!
بازوكا الصقر
Don't get separated,
لا تفترقوا وإلّا ستضيعون
Okay!
أجل
Luffy, stop Carrot!
لوفي، أوقف كاروت
I won't let you get away!
لن أسمح لكم
Duck!
انخفضوا
Take this!
تلقوا هذا
Watch out!
احذري
You...!
سحقًا لك
Cake!
الكعكة
Is this it?
أهذه نهايتنا؟
I'll eat that!
سأتناول هذه
Zeus!
زيوس
It's a delicious cloud!
إنّها غيمة لذيذة
What?
ماذا؟
Is that...
...هذا
So delicious!
لذيذة
My Weather Egg is inside of Zeus...!
بيضة الطقس الخاصة بي داخل زيوس؟
What is he doing?!
ما الذي يفعله اللعين زيوس؟
Hey, Zeus!
أنت يا زيوس
Hey, guys!
يا رفاق
Sorry we kept you waiting!
نعتذر لإبقائكم تنتظرون
Why are they...
...لِمَ هؤلاء
on the Sunny ?
على متن سفينة الساني؟
I'm sorry. Your friends aren't here. Lick!
للأسف، رفاقكما ليسوا على متن السفينة-بيرورين
Zeus Breeze...
نسيم زيوس
Tempo!
الطقس
Don't tell me Luffy and the others are...
...أيعقل أنّ لوفي والآخرين
Is that...
...ذلك
It looks like Mama finished them off with Zeus. Mama'll be here soon.
يبدو أنّ ماما قضت عليهم باستخدام زيوس، ستصل إلى هنا قريبًا
Lick!
بيرورين
He's saying that, but they'll be fine, right?
رغم ما قاله، إلّا أنّهم سيكونون بخير، صحيح؟
Yeah, I'm sure they will!
أجل، سيكونون بخير حتمًا
Lick! I guess your friends are dead,
بيرورين، أعتقد أنّ رفاقكما قد ماتوا
so what are you two gonna do?
والآن، ما الذي تنويان فعله؟
Even if you risk your lives and try to take back this ship,
حتّى إن خاطرتما بحياتكما لاستعادة السفينة، فلن يعود أحد منهم
If you want to escape from here in that submarine, I don't mind letting just the two of you leave.
إن أردتما الهرب على متن تلك الغواصة فلن أمانع مغادرتكما أنتما الاثنين فقط
No, thanks.
أرفض ذلك
Kung Fu Point!
تعزيز الكونغ فو
Get off the ship, you bastards! The Sunny is ours!
ترجلوا عن متن السفينة يا أوغاد، فسفينة الساني ملكنا
Do you want to fight?
أترغبان في خوض قتال؟
Of course!
بالطبع
We'll save the Sunny !
سنحمي سفينة الساني مهما كلّف الثمن
I guess you want to die. Lick!
يبدو أنّكما تتوقان لموتكما، بيرورين
Everyone, on your feet! Let's get this show started!
لنبدأ... العرض الصاخب المباشر
Yeah!
أجل
The forest is... What happened?!
الغابة قد... ما الذي حدث؟
Is everyone okay?!
هل الجميع بخير؟
Rabiyan, go faster!
رابيان، أسرع
Okay!
حاضر
I'm sorry I asked you to help, Sister...
...أعتذر إليكِ يا أختي، فهذا الطلب
It's okay! It's been a long time since we baked a cake together!
لا بأس، فلقد مضى وقتٌ طويل منذ أن أعددنا كعكة معًا
On top of that...
...الأهم من ذلك
You're going?! Are you kidding?!
ستذهبين؟ أتمزحين؟
Bege! Didn't I tell you?! The Straw Hats saved my younger sister Lola's life!
أخبرتك يا بيجي، لقد أنقذ طاقم قبعة القش حياة أختي الصغيرة لولا
But, Chiffon, it's dangerous! I'm worried!
لكن يا شيفون، المكان خطر، إني قلق عليك
He's right-rero ! You must escape with us-rero !
أجل، ينبغي أن نهرب معًا-ريرو
Oh, I'm sorry. That was too loud...
المعذرة، كان صوتي مرتفعًا
We can't leave without you, ma'am!
لن نرحل من دونك يا سيدتنا
Come back, Chiffon!
عُودي يا شيفون
Dangerous?! Yes, I know that!
خطر؟ إنني أعي ذلك جيّدًا
"Thank you for saving Lola." It's too easy to just say that.
«شكرًا لكم على إنقاذ حياة لولا» لكم من السهل نُطق كلماتٍ كهذه
Sincerity will be proven when you help the ones you're indebted to!
لكن الأفعال أبلغ من الأقوال حين يقع ذلك المُنقذ في مأزق
You're right, but...
...معكِ حق، ولكن
That's how you do your duty, right, darling?
هكذا نؤدي واجبنا على أكمل وجه، أليس كذلك يا عزيزي؟
If something happens to me...
...إن حدث لي مكروهٌ ما
please take care of...
فأرجو أن تعتني ببيز
Chiffon!
شيفون
Ma'am!
سيدتنا
I have to save Nami and the others and return to my family!
عليّ إنقاذ نامي ورفاقها ثم العودة إلى عائلتي
Sister! There he is!
أختي، ها هو
Pudding? Were you listening?
بودينغ، أكنتِ تصغين إلى كلامي؟
S... Sanji-san is...
...سا... سانجي-سان
S... S...
...سا... سا
Sanji...
...سانجي
S...
...سا
Sanji's there! That fool!
وجدتُ سانجي الأحمق
Say what?!
ماذا قلتِ؟
That was pretty powerful!
كان ذلك مذهلًا
My Clima-Tact isn't able to generate lightning like that!
إنّ عصا الطقس خاصتي لا تولّد صاعقةً قوية كتلك
With that much power...
...يا لها من قوة
Where's Big Mom?
أين بيغ مام؟
She must've been hit directly!
كان هجومًا مباشرًا
She's probably in that giant hole!
على الأرجح أنّها داخل تلك الحفرة الكبيرة
Did we just take down Big Mom?!
أيعقل أننا قضينا على بيغ مام؟
What is it?
ماذا؟
Wedding...
...كعكة
Big Mom's voice?!
صوت بيغ مام؟
I thought so...
كما توقعت
...cake!
الزفاف
Is she alive?!
أما زالت على قيد الحياة؟
She's not someone we can beat that easily...
إنّها ليست خصمًا يُهزم بتلك السهولة
She's climbing up!
إنّها تتسلق الحفرة
Is the hole too deep for her to climb out?
هل الحفرة عميقة لدرجة عدم قدرتها على تسلّقها؟
Let's run while she's in there!
لنهرب بينما ما تزال في داخلها
Yeah. While Big Mom can't move!
أجل، لنستغل عجز بيغ مام عن الحركة
No, she's already on her way...
كلا، إنّها متوجهة إلينا بالفعل
The ground is...
...إنّ الأرض
No way!
...أيعقل
There's no stopping Big Mom during a ravenous rampage!
لا رادع لبيغ مام عندما تُصاب بهيجان نوبة الجوع
Wedding...
...كعكة
cake!
الزفاف
Oh no! Run!
كلا، اهربوا
Wedding...
...كعكة
No... The ground's gonna crack open!
مستحيل، الأرض تتصدع
Here she comes!
إنّها قادمة
Run!
اركضوا
...cake!
الزفاف
Bring it to me!
أحضروها لي
I know you guys have it!
أعلم أنّها بحوزتكم
Straw Hat!
قبعة القش
She's at the top!
إنّها قادمة
Straw Hat crew!
طاقم قبعة القش
What?
ماذا؟
Pudding! Chiffon!
بودينغ، شيفون
Oh, Pudding! What's wrong with you?! You fooled us!
ماذا؟ بودينغ، ما الذي تريدينه منّا بعد أن خدعتنا؟
To stop Mama's ravenous rampage–
...لإيقاف هيجان نوبة جوع بماما
See? We should've tied her up earlier!
أرأيتم؟ كان علينا تقييدها آنذاك
To stop Mama's–
...من أجل إيقاف هيجان ماما
But why's Chiffon with her?! I thought she ran away with Bege's group!
ولكن لِمَ شيفون بصحبتها؟ ظننتُها هربت مع بيجي والآخرين
To stop Mama's–
...من أجل إيقاف ماما
Wanna fight?!
أتودين القتال؟
No, I don't! Listen to me!
كلا، فلتصغوا إلي
Pudding-chan, you're okay!
بودينغ-تشان، أنتِ بخير
I'm glad that your pretty face isn't hurt!
يُسعدني أنّ وجهك الظريف لم يتأذَ
So lovely! So lovely!
ظريفة، ظريفة
Pudding, get it together!
تماسكي يا بودينغ
Oh, no! Mama's coming!
احذروا، ماما قادمة
Mama!
ماما
We have no time! Pudding, get right to the point!
الوقت يُداهمنا يا بودينغ، ادخلي في صلب الموضوع
Okay!
أجل
Pathetic! You fools! You're not gonna make it!
مثيرون للشفقة، لن تلوذوا بالفرار
Even if you escape by ship,
لا فائدة حتّى لو هربتم على متن السفينة
Mama will chase you to the farthest sea and sink you to the ocean floor!
فماما ستطاردكم إلى أقاصي البحر وتُغرقكم في أعماقه
What did you say?!
ماذا قلتِ أيتها اللعينة؟
That's not right, Pudding! What are you talking about?!
كلا يا بودينغ، ما الذي تقولينه؟
You're right! You're right! What am I saying?!
كلا، كلا، ما الذي أتفوه به؟
Listen!
اسمعوا، تظن ماما أنّكم سرقتم كعكة الزفاف التي تتوق لتناولها بشدة
What?! We don't have a cake!
ماذا؟ ليست بحوزتنا أيّ كعكة
I know! But right now, Mama's in a state where she'll chase you across the ocean to get that cake!
أعلم، لكن حاليًّا ماما ستطاردكم عبر البحار إلى أن تنال كعكة الزفاف
That's right! So, Sanji! Come here!
هذا صحيح، لذا تعال معي يا سانجي
Watch as your friends get killed by Mama and go through hell!
لتتجرّع مرارة مشاهدة مقتل رفاقك على يد ماما
That's not right!
كلا، ما الذي تتفوهين به؟
If that's what you came to say, go away, you jerks!
إن كان هذا ما أتيتما لقوله، فغادرا حالًا
Wait a minute! That wasn't it!
انتظر قليلًا، أنت مخطئ
Black Leg Sanji!
الساق السوداء سانجي
What?
ماذا؟
Pudding told me you're good at making sweets, too!
أخبرتني بودينغ بأنّك ماهرٌ في إعداد الحلوى أيضًا
Yeah, I'm an excellent chef.
أجل، أنا ماهرٌ بطهي جميع أنواع الأطعمة
Okay! Then, help us bake the cake!
حسنًا، إذًا ساعدنا في إعداد الكعكة
We'll make a cake that's capable of stopping Mama,
سنعد الكعكة التي بوسعها إيقاف ماما
and then we'll help you guys escape!
وسنساعدكم على الهرب
Chiffon! Why?!
شيفون، لماذا؟
I wanna repay you for saving Lola! And I'll risk my life to do it!
أودّ رد الجميل لإنقاذكم لولا سأخاطر بحياتي من أجل ذلك
Thank you, Chiffon!
شكرًا لكِ يا شيفون
Uh-huh!
أجل
Hmph! Maybe that's the end result! But unlike my sister, I'm not doing it for you!
ربما هذه هي المسألة لكني مختلفة، إذ لا أقوم بهذا لأجل مساعدتكم
The cake that I was planning to bake for myself happened to be the one Mama is craving now!
يصدف أنّ الكعكة التي كنتُ أود إعدادها لنفسي أصبحت ما ترغب به ماما حاليًّا
A-A-And I just happened to be in this area! I didn't know you guys were here!
كـ-كما أني وجدتكم في هذا الطريق بمحض الصدفة
S-So it's not like I came all the way to stop her because I didn't want you to die, Sanji...
لـ-لذا أنا لم أقطع كل هذه المسافة لإيقافها ...لكوني لا أريدك أن تموت يا سانجي
-san !
سان-
Her emotions are like a roller coaster!
شخصيتها متقلبة بحق
I see! That's good!
فهمت، شكرًا لكما
Where can we bake the cake?!
أين سنعدّ الكعكة؟
We have extra ingredients at Chocolat Town!
لدينا مكونات إضافية في بلدة الشوكولاتة
Whole Cake Island
جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
First we'll go to Chocolat Town and bake the cake as fast as we can!
سنتجه أولًا إلى بلدة الشوكولاتة ونعدّ الكعكة بأسرع ما يمكننا
Whole Cake Island
جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
Chocolat Town Cacao Island
بلدة الشوكولاتة جزيرة الكاكاو
Then we'll carry it on a ship and deliver it to you!
وبعدها سنحملها على متن السفينة ونعطيكم إياها
And we'll let Mama, who will be chasing you, eat the cake!
ثم سنجعل ماما التي تطاردكم تتناول الكعكة
That way, we can distract her attention away from you! So just hang in there until then!
بتلك الطريقة سنشتت انتباه ماما عنكم، لذا اصمدوا حتّى ذلك الوقت
Is she coming?!
أهي قادمة؟
Wedding...
...كعكة
Once you sail out to sea, you'll have enemies in front of you, too!
حالما تبحرون ستجدون أعداءً أمامكم أيضًا
But I believe you guys can handle it!
لكني واثقة بأنّكم ستجدون حلًّا بشأنهم
We will!
أجل
Then... I'll come with you!
إذًا، سآتي معكما
What?!
ماذا؟
Yeah, hurry up and hop on!
أجل، اقفز بسرعة
W-W-Wait! Who said you could ride with us, idiot?!
مـ-مهلًا، من سمح لك بالصعود أيها الأحمق؟
...cake!
الزفاف
She got up!
لقد صعدت
The cake you guys are baking is the only way to stop Big Mom!
الكعكة التي ستعدّونها هي أملنا الوحيد في إيقاف هيجان بيغ مام
Uh-huh!
أجل
Guys!
يا رفاق، سأغادر الآن لكني سأعود حتمًا
Yeah, I know you will!
أجل، أعرف ذلك
Hey!
أنتما
Pudding!
بودينغ، شيفون
Oh no! She's gonna do it again!
سيئ، ستهاجم مجدّدًا
Get away!
ابتعدوا
What are you doing here?!
ما الذي تفعلانه عندكما؟
Luffy! I'll see you at sea!
لوفي، أراك في البحر
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
أعتمد عليك يا سانجي
Hegemony!
بلاد الجبابرة
Enough already...
...ارحمونا
That was close.
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Is everyone okay?
هل الجميع بخير؟
Let's go! The Sunny is waiting for us at the coast!
هيّا بنا، إنّ ساني بانتظارنا عند الساحل
Wait! They're going the wrong way.
مهلًا، إنّهم يسلكون الطريق الخاطئ
Rabiyan, go down again! Fly straight from the previous spot to the coastline!
اهبط مجدّدًا يا رابيان، حلّق من نقطتنا السابقة إلى ساحل البحر مباشرة
Roger!
عُلم
Luffy-kun and everyone!
لوفي-كن والآخرين
Wait! You're going the wrong way! There's a wall ahead of you!
مهلًا، هذا ليس الطريق الصحيح، فيوجد جدارٌ أمامكم
What? Pudding? It's the nice Pudding!
ماذا؟ بودينغ؟ أنتِ بودينغ اللطيفة
I thought we were going straight.
ظننت بأننا نسير للأمام مباشرة
Of course, we've been fooled.
لقد خُدعنا فعلًا
Everyone! The coastline is this way!
جميعًا، الساحل من هذا الاتجاه
Okay, let's go!
عظيم، هيّا بنا
We won't let you leave!
لن نسمح لكم
Leave them to me!
دعوا أمرهم لي
Memories Fil:
خيط الذكريات
Flashback!
العودة للماضي
Oh, I need to go shopping.
عليّ أن أذهب للتبضّع
Big Brother hit me!
ضربني أخي الكبير
I need to walk the dog.
حان الوقت لأخذ كلبي في نزهة
My son is missing. Has anyone seen him?
لقد ضاع ابني، أيعرف أحدكم أين هو؟
What's going on?
ما الذي يجري؟
In any case, let's run before it's too late!
على أيّ حال، لننطلق قبل فوات الأوان
They're memories from the previous owners
إنّها ذكريات الأرواح السابقة المغروسة في الهوميز
Those memories are returning to them temporarily.
وهي تعود إلى ذاكرتهم من جديد مؤقتًا
While they're confused, Mama has no control over them.
بما أنّهم مشتتو الذهن، فلن تسيطر عليهم ماما
So Luffy-kun and the others can escape from the woods now.
بوسع لوفي والآخرون الخروج من الغابة الآن
I see. Thank you, Pudding-chan!
فهمت، شكرًا لكِ يا بودينغ-تشان
Why?! How long have you been there, Sanji...
...لماذا؟ منذ متى وأنت هنا يا سانجي
-san ?!
سان؟-
Well, just for a little bit.
حسنًا، قبل فترة وجيزة
What?!
ماذا؟
How did you not notice?!
ألم تلاحظي ذلك؟
Now, Pudding-chan, let's rush to Chocolat Town.
والآن يا بودينغ-تشان، لنسرع إلى بلدة الشوكولاتة
J-Jump off and swim, you idiot!
ا-انزل واتبعنا سباحة أيها الأحمق
Your eye is beautiful even when you're mad...
عينكِ جميلة حتّى حينما تغضبين
Are you okay, Pudding?
هل أنتِ بخير يا بودينغ؟
I-I'm fine... D-D-Don't mess with me!
أ-أنا بخير، لا-لا تعبث معي
O-Or I'll kill you, Sanji...
...وإ-وإلّا قتلتك يا سانجي
-san !
سان-
I see the coastline ahead!
أرى الساحل أمامنا
Hurry up!
أسرعوا
We made it! But... is Pudding really on our side now?!
لقد نجونا، لكن أحقًّا بودينغ في جانبنا؟
I don't know! We shouldn't lower our guard until we escape their territory!
لا أعلم، لذا حريّ بنا ألّا نرخي دفاعنا إلى أن نخرج من منطقتهم
I won't let you get away!
لن أسمح لكم بالهرب
Hey, Zeus!
يا زيوس
How could you do that?!
كيف عساك تفعل ذلك؟
Why did you hit us, too?!
لِمَ قمت بضربنا؟
I'm sorry... I didn't mean for that to happen...
المعذرة، لم أكن أنوي ذلك
I don't care what you meant to do! You better pay attention next time!
لا تهمني نيّتك، إيّاك أن تغفل مرة أخرى
Yes, you're right...
أجل، فهمت
But they were so delicious... Those thundercloud eggs.
مع ذلك فبيض السحابة الرعدية تلك كان لذيذًا للغاية
Huh?!
ماذا؟
Hey, are you really listening to me?! Mama's orders are absolute!
هل فهمت حقًّا؟ إنّ أوامر ماما مُطلقة
I know...
قلتُ لك فهمت
Give it to me!
...أعطوني
My wedding cake!
كعكة الزفاف خاصتي
Oh, no!
سيئ
Dodge it!
تفادوها
Damn...
سحقًا
That was close!
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Thank you, Jinbe!
شكرًا لك يا جينبي
You're quite the match for our Chess Peacekeepers, skeleton...
إنّك تبلي حسنًا بمواجهة جنود الشطرنج أيها الهيكل العظمي
It's because I am...
...هذا لأني
Soul King!
ملك السول
Enemies keep coming out of the mirror...
يواصل الأعداء التدفق من المرآة
They're coming from the mirror in Nami and Robin's room. Will they be mad if we break it?
إنّها مرآة غرفة نامي وروبين، هل ستغضبان إن كسرناها؟
If we can break it, let's break it. We'll apologize later.
علينا كسرها إن استطعنا، وسنعتذر لهما لاحقًا
Who are you gonna apologize to? Lick.
لِمن ستعتذران-بيرورين؟
You saw the lightning earlier, didn't you?
لقد رأيتما الصاعقة منذ قليل
None of them are returning to this ship.
لن يعود أحدٌ إلى هذه السفينة
I've been saying that I want to show mercy on you two.
إنني أعرض عليكما بعض الرحمة
No matter how hard you try, our soldiers will come through the mirror endlessly.
مهما قاتلتما، فسيستمر جنودنا بالتدفق
And you guys will use up all of your energy eventually.
وستخور قواكما عاجلًا أم آجلًا
If you submit right here, right now, I'll at least spare your life...
أمّا إن استسلمتما هنا والآن، فسأعفو عن حياتكما على الأقل
Just give up already.
استسلما فحسب
What a foolish conversation.
يا له من حوارٍ عقيم
We're sick and tired of responding to that.
لقد سئمنا من ترديد إجابتنا لك
We just want you to get off of our ship.
لذا أرجو أن تغادروا السفينة
The Sunny is our ship!
فإن سفينة الساني سفينتنا
Do you really wanna fight me?
أتودان مواجهتي حقًّا؟
I see...
فهمت
It seems you don't really value your own life...
يبدو أنّكما لا تأبهان بحياتكما حقًّا
All right.
لا بأس
I'll kill you with my own hands.
سأقتلكما بيدي هاتين
Lick.
بيرورين
Oh! That's the edge of the forest!
إنّها نهاية الغابة
All right! Let's go straight to Cacao Island!
حسنًا، لنذهب إلى جزيرة الكاكو مباشرة
Brook! Chopper!
بروك وتشوبر
Is that your ship?
أتلك سفينتكم؟
Yeah, it's getting attacked.
أجل، إنّها تتعرض للهجوم
I guess they were ambushed...
أظنهم نصبوا كمينًا لكم
Oh, no! Our older brothers are there!
مصيبة، أخوانا الكبيران على متنها
Our older brothers are attacking Sanji-san's friends...
...أخوانا يهاجمان رفاق سانجي-سان
Hmph! Your friends are screwed!
قُضي عليهما، يستحقان ذلك
Your friends will be swallowed by the sea!
سيغرق رفيقاك في أعماق البحر
What are you saying, Pudding?!
ما الذي تتفوهين به يا بودينغ؟
Oh, no! That's not what I meant to say!
كلا، لم أكن أقصد قول ذلك
What do you wanna do? Should we go down to the ship?
لكن ماذا ستفعل؟ أتود العودة إلى السفينة؟
No, I'll come along with Pudding-chan.
كلا، سأرافق بودينغ-تشان
What?
ماذا؟
Are you sure? We'll keep on going then!
أأنت متأكد؟ سنواصل المضي إذًا
Yeah, we don't need to worry about them.
أجل، لا داعي للقلق عليهما
Instead, let's get started...
...وبدلًا من ذلك، لنستعجل
on the cake that will make Big Mom faint!
بإعداد الكعكة التي ستُفقد بيغ مام وعيها من لذّتها